{
    "title": "Super Friday Quiz",
    "marking-occurs": "at-quiz-end",
    "rounds": [{
        "name": "Setup",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Enter your name:",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Any"
        }]
    },{
        "name": "Music Round",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "What year was the original Live Aid?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "1985"
        }, {
            "question": "Which singer‚Äôs real name was Farrokh Bulsara?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Freddie Mercury"
        }, {
            "question": "Which huge, modern day British artist was born in Halifax, Yorkshire?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Ed Sheeran"
        }, {
            "question": "Rocketman is a 2019 biographical musical film based on the life of which British musician?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Elton John"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the name of Amy Winehouse's debut album?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Frank"
        }, {
            "question": "In which city did The Courteeners from?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Manchester"
        }, {
            "question": "What hit single did Queen release in 1975 on the album, A Night at the Opera?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody"
        }, {
            "question": "Which famous British band was named first as Pectoralz?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Coldplay"
        }, {
            "question": "Keith Richards and Mick Jagger are songwriters of many songs of which band?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Rolling Stones"
        }, {
            "question": "Kashmir is the famous song by which English Rock band?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Led Zeppelin"
        }]
    },{
        "name": "Geography Round",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "What is the largest country in South America?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Brazil"
        }, {
            "question": "What country is called Land of Fire and Ice?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Iceland"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the only territory of the mainland Americas that still belongs to a European country?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "French Guiana"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the highest active volcano in Europe?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Mount Etna"
        }, {
            "question": "Which city is also known as The Eternal City?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Rome"
        }, {
            "question": "Baku is the capital city of which eastern European country?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Azarbaijan"
        }, {
            "question": "Which country‚Äôs name could be part of a Christmas dinner?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Turkey"
        }, {
            "question": "What did Ceylon change its name to in 1972?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Sri Lanka"
        }, {
            "question": "On the London Tube network, which is the only station to begin with the letter i?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Ickenham"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the largest desert in the world?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Antarctica"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "London Eatery Round üá¨üáß",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "At which restaurant can you enjoy your meal in total darkness and be served by blind waiters?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Dans Le Noir"
        }, {
            "question": "Where would you find critically acclaimed Turkish restaurant Black Axe Mangal?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "islington"
        }, {
            "question": "Where can you eat the famous Venimoo burger, loaded with beef & venison patties & b√©arnaise sauce?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Mac & Wild"
        }, {
            "question": "Which London restaurant is famous for its 'press for champagne' button?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Bob Bob Ricard"
        }, {
            "question": "Which world-famous restaurant can be found at 68 Royal Hospital Rd?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Restaurant Gordon Ramsay"
        }, {
            "question": "Which celeb hotspot is famous for its crab doughnuts?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Chiltern Firehouse"
        }, {
            "question": "Mele e Pere is known for serving which type of cuisine?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Italian"
        }, {
            "question": "Chinese restaurant Chai Wu can be found in which famous store?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Harrods"
        }, {
            "question": "Which restaurant  is believed to be London's oldest restaurant?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Rules, Established in 1798"
        }, {
            "question": "MasterChef winner Thomasina Miers founded which restaurant chain?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Wahaca"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Business Quiz ",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Which company was originally called Cadabra, like the magic term ‚Äúabracadabra‚Äù?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Amazon"
        }, {
            "question": "Which company‚Äôs first name was BackRub?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Google"
        }, {
            "question": "Netflix founders Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph offered to sell the company which company? ",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Blockbuster"
        }, {
            "question": "Who famously advised zuckerberg to drop ‚ÄúThe‚Äù from ‚ÄúThe Facebook?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Sean Parker"
        }, {
            "question": "Widely used Prefix NS in Objective C is based on which OS developed by Job‚Äôs old company he built after being fired from Apple?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Next Step"
        }, {
            "question": "Which Microblogging platform and social networking website founded by David Karp in 2007?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Tumblr"
        }, {
            "question": "M&S was founded in 1884 by Michael Marks and Thomas Spencer in which city?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Leeds"
        }, {
            "question": "In 1928, M&S entered into long-term relationships with British manufacturers, and sold clothes and food under which brand all these happened in 1928?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "St Michael"
        }, {
            "question": "The uncompromising attitude towards customer relations was summarised by the which 1953 slogan?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "The customer is always and completely right!"
        }, {
            "question": "The company expanded internationally with which country in 1973?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Canada"
        }]
    }]
}
